Guide to the Sherman Kent Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional Material, 1917-1991; Accession 1997-M-183
  - Writings
    - Reminiscences of a Varied Life
      - Printed copy, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Reviews by Kent of articles and books, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Short fictional pieces, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 39-40)
    - Speech, 1930s (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Strategic Intelligence ...
      - Pre-publication correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Princeton University Press, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Reviews, 1949-1950 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Subject files
    - French history [notes], n.d. (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Intelligence
      - 1945 (Box 3, Folder 46-49)
      - 1946-1947, 1949, undated (Box 4, Folder 50-52)
    - Yale teaching [History 10a], 1949 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Personal papers
    - Friends School [student papers and memorabilia], 1917-1918 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Kent family [papers and clippings], 1938, 1976, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Photographs, ca. 1942, 1960s, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Additional Material, 1831-1852; Accession 2014-M-032
  This accession consists of four volumes of data from the French national censuses of 1842 for agriculture and 1852 for industry; one volume containing results for the Chamber of Deputies elections of 1831, 1834, 1837, 1839, 1842, and 1846; and one volume of hand-drawn maps of each territorial department with the cantons outlined. The data was compiled by Sherman Kent.
  - Agricultural census data, 1842 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - Industrial census data, 1852 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Territorial department maps, undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Chamber of Deputies election data, 1831-1846 (Box 4, Folder 1-3)